Finding Aid for Muschenheim, William. Architectural drawings and papers. 1925-1990
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Project Files
  - Job 92, William B.F. Drew
    - [William B.F. Drew residence (Westhampton Beach, N.Y.). Decoration. Furniture]
      - Drawings, #.002134-.02265, .02953 April 1946-August 1947, 133 sheets: various media; or smaller 93.5 x 149.7 cm.; 36-7/8 x 58-7/8 inches
        - Laundry lay-out and bath recesses [showing elevations, plan, and sections, with notes and measurements]: Drawing 22 01/30/1947 revised 2/5/1947, NYDA.1986.004.02183
        - Mirror details [showing elevations and sections, with notes and measurements]: Drawing 23, 2/6/1947, NYDA.1986.004.02184
        - Misc. details [of wall brackets in dining rm. showing an elevation and section, and a plan of a shelf in the powder room, with notes and measurements]: Drawing 24, 2/17/1947, NYDA.1986.004.02185
        - Tea-cart and tables "A" and "B" showing an elevation and axonometric views with notes and measurements]: Drawing 25, 2/20/1947, NYDA.1986.004.02186
        - [Tea-cart and tables "A" and "B" showing axonometric views with notes and measurements]., NYDA.1986.004.02187
        - Details of rolling laundry basket [showing a plan, elevations, and sections, with notes and measurements] :Drawing 26, 2/24/1947, NYDA.1986.004.02188
        - Standing lamp for enclosed porch [showing an elevation and plan, with notes and measurements]: Drawing 27, 2/24/1947, NYDA.1986.004.02189
        - Folding table in laundry [showing an elevation, plan, and sections, with notes and measurements]: Drawing 28, 2/27/1947, NYDA.1986.004.02190
        - Lumiline reflectors for owner's rm. and guest rm. [showing elevations and a F.S.D. section, with notes and measurements]: Drawing 29, 3/4/1947, NYDA.1986.004.02191
        - Table lamp for living rm. [showing a diametric(?) view, plan, elevations, and a section, with notes and measurements]: Drawing 30, 3/12/1947, NYDA.1986.004.02192
        - Table lamp for living rm. [showing a diametric(?) view, plan, elevations, and a section, with notes and measurements]: Drawing 30 3/12/1947 Blackline print with pastel on paper., NYDA.1986.004.02193
        - Table #8 with glass top [showing a diametric(?) view, elevation and plan, with notes and measurements]: Drawing 31, 3/24/1947, NYDA.1986.004.02194
        - Sliding panels for side-board [showing a section and elevation, with notes and measurements.]: Drawing 32, 4/7/1947, NYDA.1986.004.02195
        - Shelves and drawers in side-board [showing a section and elevation, with notes and measurements]: Drawing 32-A, 4/30/1947, NYDA.1986.004.02196
        - Plot plan (planting lay-out) [with notes]: Drawing 33 5/1/1947, NYDA.1986.004.02197
          (Verso notes "Swan River Oak Park.")
        - Plot plan (planting lay-out) [with notes]: Drawing 33, 5/1/47, revised 5/20/1947, NYDA.1986.004.02198
        - Plot plan (planting lay-out) [with notes]: Drawing 33, 5/1/47, revised 5/20/1947, NYDA.1986.004.02199; Blueprint on paper.
        - Flower pot holder [showing a plan and side and front elevations, with notes and measurements]: Drawing 34, 5/8/1947, NYDA.1986.004.02200
        - Flower pot holder [showing a plan and side and front elevations, with notes and measurements]: Drawing 34 05/08/1947, NYDA.1986.004.02201; Blueprint on paper.
        - D't'ls of fluorescent fixture and cleats on roof for ladder [showing an exterior elevation at kitchen entrance and F.S.D.'s, with notes and measurements]: Drawing 35, 6/5/1947, NYDA.1986.004.02202
        - Lumiline fixt. for liv. rm. desk [showing an elevation of the desk and a F.S.D. section of the fixture, with notes and measurements]: Drawing 36, 6/3/1947, NYDA.1986.004.02203
        - [Study for living room desk showing an elevation]., NYDA.1986.004.02204
        - Platform facing ocean at crest of dune [showing a plan and section, with notes and measurements]: Drawing 37, 7/16/1947, NYDA.1986.004.02205
        - Platform facing ocean at crest of dune [showing a plan and section, with notes and measurements]: Drawing 37 07/16/1947, NYDA.1986.004.02206; Blueprint on paper.
        - Tables for south terrace [showing a plan, elevations, and a section, with notes and measurements]: Drawing 38 / E.S., 8/29/1947, NYDA.1986.004.02207
        - Sketch of possible duct lay-out in basement [showing a plan with notes and measurements], 8/16/1946, NYDA.1986.004.02208
        - Dining room [showing plan and detail sections, with notes and measurements]., NYDA.1986.004.02209
        - [Study of laundry rm. showing a plan with measurements]., NYDA.1986.004.02210
        - [Study of stair hall showing a plan and detail elevations, with notes and measurements]., NYDA.1986.004.02211
        - [Study of liv. rm. showing a plan with measurements.], NYDA.1986.004.02212
        - [Study of the porch(?) showing a plan with measurements]., NYDA.1986.004.02213
        - [Study of a fireplace(?) showing a plan with measurements]., NYDA.1986.004.02214
        - [Unidentified study showing a plan with a fireplace, with measurements]., NYDA.1986.004.02215
        - Rug for guest rm. [showing a plan]., NYDA.1986.004.02216
        - [Unidentified study showing plans of door jamb(?) and partitions, with notes and measurements]., NYDA.1986.004.02217
        - [Unidentified studies with measurements]., NYDA.1986.004.02218
        - [Sketch of a laundry machine(?) showing a plan with measurements]., NYDA.1986.004.02219
        - [Unfinished study of a bar(?) showing a plan with measurements]., NYDA.1986.004.02220
        - [Studies of interior elevations of the master, north, south, and guest baths, with notes and measurements]., NYDA.1986.004.02221
        - [Study of windows in the enclosed porch and dng. rm. showing an elevation with measurements]., NYDA.1986.004.02222
        - [Study of windows for the dressing rm. or master's bed rm. and guest rm. showing an elevation with measurements]., NYDA.1986.004.02223
        - [Study of stair hall landing(?) showing elevation of door and windows]., NYDA.1986.004.02224
        - [Sketches of door and window showing elevations with measurements]., NYDA.1986.004.02225
        - [Study of window groups along enclosed porch showing detail elevations(?) with notes and measurements]., NYDA.1986.004.02226
        - [Study of a chair showing an axonometric view]., NYDA.1986.004.02227
        - [Study of a cushioned chair showing an axonometric view with notes and measurements]., NYDA.1986.004.02228
        - [Study of a cushioned chair showing an isometric view with measurements]., NYDA.1986.004.02229
        - [Study of studio couch showing an axonometric view and detail elevations, with notes and measurements]., NYDA.1986.004.02230
        - [Study of a segmental settee showing an isometric view, with notes and measurements]., NYDA.1986.004.02231
        - [Study of guest room chest showing an axonometric view and a bed showing an end elevation, with measurements]., NYDA.1986.004.02232
        - [Study of master bedroom chests showing axonometric views and a bed showing an elevation, with measurements]., NYDA.1986.004.02233
        - [Study of chest of drawers with measurements]., NYDA.1986.004.02234
        - [Study of a refrigerator cabinet(?) showing an axonometric view with measurements]., NYDA.1986.004.02235
        - North [exterior] elevation / Leonard L. Bishop, Architect. Drawing noted "Residence for Mr. Wm. A. Drew"., NYDA.1986.004.02236
        - [East and west exterior elevations] / [Leonard L. Bishop, Architect]., NYDA.1986.004.02237
        - South [exterior] elevation / [Leonard L. Bishop, Architect]., NYDA.1986.004.02238
        - Basement and foundation plan [with notes and measurements] / [Leonard L. Bishop, Architect]., NYDA.1986.004.02239
        - First floor plan [with notes and measurements] / Leonard L. Bishop, Architect., NYDA.1986.004.02240
        - Second floor plan [with notes and measurements] / Leonard L. Bishop, Architect., NYDA.1986.004.02241
        - Heating [shown in basement floor plan and detail sections, with notes and measurements]: W.D. 1 / J.L. Murphy Inc. Contr's.; dwn. by A.S. 06/10/1946 rev., 08/23/1946 9/8/1946, NYDA.1986.004.02242
        - Heating [shown in basement floor plan and a detail section, with notes and measurements]: W.D. 1 / J.L. Murphy Inc. Contr's; dwn. by A.S. 06/10/1946 rev., 08/23/1946 9/8/1946, NYDA.1986.004.02243
        - Part. plan of equipment room [with notes and measurements]: Part of Drawing W.D. 1, rev. 5 / [J.L. Murphy Inc.] 12/11/1946, NYDA.1986.004.02252
        - Heating and ventilating [shown in first floor plan and detail sections, with notes and measurements]: W.D. 2 / J.L. Murphy Inc. Contr's.; dwn. by A.S. 06/10/1946 rev., 8/19/1946 9/7/1946, NYDA.1986.004.02244
        - [Duplicate copy of 1986.004.02244]., NYDA.1986.004.02245
        - Heating and ventilation [shown in 2nd floor plan and detail sections, with notes and measurements]: W.D. 3 / J.L. Murphy Inc. Contr's.; dwn. by A.S., 6/10/46, rev. 08/19/1946 9/7/1946, NYDA.1986.004.02246
        - [Duplicate copy of 1986.004.02246]., NYDA.1986.004.02247
        - Heating and air cond. [shown in attic plan and detail, with notes and measurements]: W.D. 4 / J.L. Murphy Inc. Contr's.; dwn. by A.S. 06/12/1946 rev., 08/22/1946 9/7/1946, NYDA.1986.004.02248
        - [Duplicate copy of 1986.004.02248]., NYDA.1986.004.02249
        - [Partial plans and elevations with detail sections of basement and first floor, with notes and measurements]: Job 22308 W.D. 5 / J.L. Murphy Inc.; dwn. by G.M., 9/9/1946, NYDA.1986.004.02250
        - [Basement and first floor showing partial plans, elevations and detail sections, with notes and measurements]: Job 22308 W.D. 5 / J.L. Murphy Inc.; dwn. by G.M., 9/9/1946, NYDA.1986.004.02251
        - Cutting locations for ducts [shown in basement floor plan and details, with notes and measurements]: W.D. 6 / [J.L. Murphy Inc. Contr's.]; [dwn. by] A.S., 9/19/1946, NYDA.1986.004.02253
        - Duct opening locations [shown on first floor plan, with notes and measurements]: W.F. 7 / [J.L. Murphy Inc.]; [dwn. by] A.S., 9/19/1946, NYDA.1986.004.02254
        - Duct opening locations [shown on second floor plan, with notes and measurements]: W.D. 8 / [J.L. Murphy Inc.]; [dwn. by A.S.], 9/23/1946, NYDA.1986.004.02255
        - [Lighting] type "A" and "C" [showing a plan, elevation, and sections, with notes and measurements]: Proj. no. 186 / Ledlin Light Designers Inc.; dwn. by K.Y., O.K. 12/12/1946 W.M., NYDA.1986.004.02256
        - [Lighting] type "A" and "C" [showing a plan, elevation, and sections, with notes and measurements]: Proj. no. 186 / Ledlin Light Designers Inc.; dwn. by K.Y., O.K. as noted 02/05/1947 W.M., NYDA.1986.004.02257
        - [Lighting] type "B", "D" and "E" [showing an elevation and sections, with notes and measurements]: Proj. no. 186 / Ledlin Light Designers Inc.; dwn. by K.Y. 11/22/1946, NYDA.1986.004.02258
        - [Lighting] type "F" and "Fa" [showing section with notes and measurements]: Proj. no. 186 / Ledlin Light Designers Inc.; dwn. by K.Y. 11/23/1946, NYDA.1986.004.02259
        - [Lighting] type "G" and "H" [showing sections, with notes and measurements]: Proj. no. 186 / Ledlin Light Designers Inc.; K.Y. 11/23/1946, NYDA.1986.004.02260
        - [Lighting type "H" [showing a section, with notes and measurements]: Proj. no. 186 / Ledlin Light Designers Inc.; H.G. 12/29/1946, NYDA.1986.004.02261
        - [Lighting] type "K" and "L" [showing a plan and sections, with notes and measurements]: Proj. no. 186 / Ledlin Light Designers Inc.; K.Y. 11/23/1946, NYDA.1986.004.02262
        - [Lighting] type "M" [showing a section, with notes and measurements]: Proj. no. 186 / Ledlin Light Designers Inc.; dwn. by K.Y. 11/23/1946, NYDA.1986.004.02263
        - [Lighting fixture showing a section with notes and measurements]: Proj. no. 186 / Ledlin Light Designers Inc.; dwn. by H.G., 2/27/1947, NYDA.1986.004.02264
        - [Lighting fixture showing a section with notes and measurements]: Proj. no. 186 / Ledlin Light Designers Inc.; dwn. by K.Y., 3/27/1947, NYDA.1986.004.02265
      - Papers
        - 1 Dr. 311: (Box A14, Folder 92-4)
          (1 page of computations)
        - drawings, 25 sheets (Box A14, Folder 92-11)
          (1 small page of notes.)
        - surveys (Box A14, Folder 92-13)
          (7 sheets) (4 pages of notes)
        - archival, Samples and Specs.: (Box A14, Folder 92-14)
          (color samples, specifications)
        - archival, Estimates: (Box A15, Folder 92-15)
          (Worked with: Westhampton Farms, Frank A. Swerdzewski (landscape gardener), Edgar V. Bythiner (rugs, tiles), Federal Carpet Co., Miller Durable Floors, Inc., Knit-Wood Shade & Screen Co., Ledlin Light Designers, Inc., and others.)
        - archival, Bills: (Box A15, Folder 92-16)
          (receipts, invoices, bills, etc. Worked with: Gustav F. Wild (glass, mirrors), Ledlin Light Designers, Inc., H.B. Lehman-Connor Co., Inc. (upholstery and drapery fabrics), P.E. Guerin (hardware for furniture & interiors), Loosen & Brautigam (cabinet makers), F. Schumacher & Co. (carpets, wallpapers), and many others.)
        - archival, Accounts: (Box A15, Folder 92-17)
          (statements, certificates, orders.)
        - archival, Correspondence: (Box A15, Folder 92-18)
          (correspondence, samples. Corresponded with: William B.F. Drew, F. Earl Mueller, and others.)
        - archival, 1 ink sketch attached to letter: (Box A15, Folder 92-19)
          (1 drawing of elevation of center south window in living room.)
        - Surveys, archival materials (Box A15, Folder 92-21)
          (found in 'surveys' drawing file, moved 1/93: notes, receipts, outlines of proposed alterations, 2 drawings of chairs, correspondence.)
        - prints (Box A15, Folder 92-22)
          (Folder 16)
          (B&W photographs showing interior of residence (7 items), B&W photographs showing exterior of residence (2 items), color photographs showing interior of residence (4 items).)
      - Photographs (Box B10)
    - [Women's dormitory 1-A and 1-B (Elza, Tenn.). Coiling doors]
      - Drawings, #.02266, 1 drawings blackline print on paper; or smaller 54.2 x 74 cm.; 21-3/8 x 29-1/8 inches
        - [Detail of horizontal rolling fronts, U.S. government women's dormitory 1-A and 1-B, Elza, Tenn. [graphic]: [elevations and detail sections] / Stone and Webster Engr. Corp.; Foster and Creighton Co., contractor; J.G. Wilson Corp.[manufacturer]; drawn by E.C. Rogers. Order no.78509. Sheet no. 1 in set 1.], NYDA.1986.004.02266
          (This Drawing was found in Muschenheim Job no. 92, folder 12.)
  - Job 93, Shinnecock Tower
    - [Shinnecock Tower (Hampton Bays, N.Y.). Alterations]
      - Drawings, #.02267 August 14, 1946, 1 blueprints blueprint on paper; or smaller 64.6 x 41.8 cm.; 25-1/2 x 16-1/2 inches
        - Drawing, August 14, 1946, NYDA.1986.004.02267
      - Photographs
        - Lighthouse (Box B10)
  - Job 94, Thomas A. Morgan
    - [Thomas A. Morgan residence, 217 East 62nd Street (New York, N.Y.) Plant stand]
      - Drawings, #.02268-.02270 October 23, 1946, 3 sheets: various media; or smaller 43.3 x 56.1 cm.; 17-1/8 x 22-1/8 inches
        This set consists of 1 pencil on tracing paper, 1 blueprint on paper, and 1 pencil on paper.
        - Details of flower stand [showing plans, an elevation, an oblique view and a full size detail section, with notes and measurements]: Drawing 1 10/23/1946, NYDA.1986.004.02268
        - Details of flower stand [showing plans, an elevation, an oblique view and a full size detail section, with notes and measurements]: Drawing 1 10/23/1946, NYDA.1986.004.02269; Blueprint on paper.
        - [Study of a mantel(?) showing an elevation and detail]., NYDA.1986.004.02270
      - Papers
        - archival, Accounts: (Box A16, Folder 94-2)
          (4 statements, 1 accounts chart.)
  - Job 95, Eduardo Andrade
    - [Eduardo Andrade apartment, 215 East 72nd Street (New York, N.Y.)]
      - Drawings, #.02271-.02278 October-December 1946, 8 sheets: various media; or smaller 66.8 x 86 cm.; 26-1/4 x 33-7/8 inches
        This set consists of 5 pencil on tracing paper, 2 blueprints on paper, and 1 pencil on paper.
        - Book-shelves [showing a] plan and elevations [with notes and measurements]: Drawing 1A 10/11/1946, NYDA.1986.004.02271
        - Book-shelves [showing a] plan and elevations [and a F.S.D. section, with notes and measurements]: Drawing 1A 10/11/1946 revised, 10/31/1946, NYDA.1986.004.02272
        - Radiator enclosures in living rm. [showing a cross section and an elevation, with notes and measurements]: Drawing 2 12/10/1946, NYDA.1986.004.02273
        - Wood valence [sic], reflector, and rad. encl's in liv. rm. [showing an elevation and a F.S.D. section, with notes and measurements]: Drawing 3, 1/2/1947, NYDA.1986.004.02274
        - [Sketch of laid-out elevations with notes]., NYDA.1986.004.02275
          (Verso also shows notes.)
        - [Sketches of sections showing lighting]., NYDA.1986.004.02276
        - [Sketches of unidentified sections]., NYDA.1986.004.02277
        - [Lumiline lamp shown in a F.S. section with notes and measurements]., NYDA.1986.004.02278
      - Papers
        - Surveys, 4 sheets: (Box A16, Folder 95-2)
          (3 small pages of notes, 1 confirmation of quote for brass knobs.)
        - archival, Accounts: (Box A16, Folder 95-3)
          (correspondence with Mr. & Mrs. Eduardo Andrade and others; statements; certificates; orders; and other accounts material.)
  - Job 96, Stiesel Medicinal Soap Co
    - [Stiesel Medicinal Soap Company (Preston Hollow, N.Y.). Soap. Design drawings]
      - Drawings, #.02279-.02281 December 13, 1946, 3 sheets: various media; or smaller 45 x 56.3 cm.; 17-3/4 x 22-1/8 inches
        This set consists of 2 pencil on tracing paper, and 1 blackline print on paper. The soap was called "Cherbel".
        - Soap cake [showing a] plan, elevations, and isometric [i.e. axonometric] views [with notes and measurements]: Drawing 1 12/12/1946, NYDA.1986.004.02279
        - Soap cake [showing a] plan, elevations, and isometric [i.e. axonometric] views [with notes and measurements]: Drawing 1 12/12/1946, NYDA.1986.004.02280
        - [Soap cake design showing a plan, elevations and an axonometric view]., NYDA.1986.004.02281
  - Job 97, Edgar V. Bythiner
    - Edgar V. Bythiner, 119 Payson Ave., NYC 1947
      - Papers
        - archival, Accounts: (Box A16, Folder 97-1)
          (1 statement, 1 accounts chart)
  - Job 98, untitled
    - No title given in WM's files 1947
      - Papers
        - Accounts: (Box A16, Folder 98-1)
          (1 accounts chart)
  - Job 99, Trinity Operating Co.
    - [Trinity Operating Company, Inc., 75 Varick Street (New York, N.Y.). Lobby. Alterations]
      - Drawings, #,02282-.02284 April 1947, 3 sheets: various media; or smaller 65.4 x 83.6 cm.; 25-3/4 x 33 inches
        This set consists of 2 blueprints on paper, and 1 pencil on tracing paper. Trinity Operating Company was based at 74 Trinity Place, New York 6, N.Y.
        - Proposed alteration to first floor lobby [showing a floor plan, typical interior elevation, exterior elevation, oblique views of light fixtures and a painting schedule, with notes and measurements]: Drawing 1 / by H.R.L. 4/2/1947, NYDA.1986.004.02282
        - Proposed alteration to first floor lobby [showing a floor plan, typical interior elevation, exterior elevation, oblique views of light fixtures and a painting schedule, with notes and measurements]: Drawing 1 / by H.R.L. 4/2/1947, NYDA.1986.004.02283; Blueprint on paper.
        - Diamond grilles design S-15 [and] S-16 [with] square and sanitary slots [showing an elevation] / Diamond Manufacturing Company., NYDA.1986.004.02284
      - Papers
        - archival, Estimates: (Box A16, Folder 99-3)
          (2 pages of estimates, 1 page of computations)
        - archival, Accounts: (Box A16, Folder 99-4)
          (2 statements, 1 accounts chart, 1 small page of notes.)
        - archival, Correspondence: (Box A16, Folder 99-5)
          (correspondence, memos. Corresponded with: J. Fullerton Brown. Memos from the Trinity Operating Co.)
        - archival (Box A16, Folder 99-6)
          (archival material found with drawings Folder 2: paint samples, 11 pages of notes, 1 business card.)
  - Job 100, Miss Bertha Meyer
    - [Bertha Meyer cottage (Loveland, Colo.)]
      - Drawings, #.02285 April 2, 1947, 1 drawings pencil with pastel on tracing paper; or smaller 43.8 x 56.4 cm.; 17-1/2 x 22-1/4 inches
        - Drawing, April 2, 1964, NYDA.1986.004.02285
  - Job 101, Prof. Martin Bernstein
    - Martin Bernstein apartment, 302 West 12th St. NYC 1948-1950
      - Drawings, #.02286-.02313, 28 sheets: various media; or smaller 65 x 84.8 cm.; 25-5/8 x 33-3/8 inches
        This set consists of 10 pencil and 4 pencil with pastel on tracing paper; and 4 pencil, 2 pencil with pastel, 1 pencil with pastel and ink, 1 ink, 1 blueprint, 2 blueprints with pastel, 1 blackline print with pastel and 2 blackline prints with pastel and ink on paper.
        - Study: [north, south, east and west interior] elevs. and d't'ls of new shelves, furniture, etc. [with notes and measurements]: Drawing 1 08/17/1948 revised, 8/26/1948, NYDA.1986.004.02286
        - Study: [north, south, east and west interior] elevs. and d't'ls of new shelves, furniture, etc. [with notes and measurements]: Drawing 1 08/17/1948 revised 8/26/1948, NYDA.1986.004.02287; Blackline print with pastel and ink on paper.
        - Study: details of desk, wall and liquor cabinets [showing plans, elevations, and sections, with notes and measurements]: Drawing 2 8/30/1948, NYDA.1986.004.02288
        - Study: d't'ls of low table [showing plans, an elevation and a F.S.D.] and lamp shield [showing a plan and elevation, with notes and measurements]: Drawing 3 9/8/1948, NYDA.1986.004.02289
        - Study: details of drawer cabinet [showing an isometric view, a section, and F.S.D.'s, with notes and measurements]: Drawing 4 8/17/1949, NYDA.1986.004.02290
        - Living rm.: plan, [north, south, east, and west interior] elevations, and d't'ls of woodwork [with notes and measurements]: Drawing 5 10/10/1949 revised, 10/19/1949, NYDA.1986.004.02291
        - Living rm.: plan, [north, south, east, and west interior] elevations, and d't'ls of woodwork [with notes and measurements]: Drawing 5 10/10/1949 revised, 10/19/1949, NYDA.1986.004.02292
        - Liv. rm.: carpet lay-out [showing scheme 1 and 2]: Drawing 5-A 11/14/1949, NYDA.1986.004.02293
        - Liv. rm.: details of side-board [showing a plan, front elevation, detail section and an elev. of end of radio cabinet, with notes and measurements]: Drawing 6, 11/2/1949, NYDA.1986.004.02294
        - Liv. rm.: details of love seat [showing a plan and end elevation, with notes and measurements]: Drawing 7, 11/3/1949, NYDA.1986.004.02295
        - Liv. rm.: details of love seat [showing a plan and end elevation, with notes and measurements]: Drawing 7, 11/3/1949, NYDA.1986.004.02296; Blueprint on paper.
        - Living room: plan and sections of silver drawer and small table [showing plans, elevations and sections, with notes and measurements]: Drawing 8 / [drawn by S.S.] 11/17/1949 revised, 11/23/1949, NYDA.1986.004.02297
        - Liv. rm.: details of table lamp [showing a plan, front and side elevations with notes and measurements]: Drawing 9 1/16/1950, NYDA.1986.004.02298
        - Living rm. and dining alcove: plan [noted with alterations and measurements]: File 5, Drawing 2-B., NYDA.1986.004.02299R
          (This Drawing represents Muschenheim's own apt. 3E. He apparently used it as a typical floor plan for alterations in apt. 4E.)
        - [Axonometric sketches of a radio cabinet and phonograph, with measurements], NYDA.1986.004.02299V